Did you hear that?
They shut down the main reactor. We'll be destroyed for sure.
This is madness.
We're doomed.
There'll be no escape for the princess this time.
What's that?
R2-D2, where are you?
At last. Where have you been?
They're heading in this direction. What are we going to do?
We'll be sent to the Kessel spice mines or smashed into who knows what.
Wait a minute. Where are you going?
The Death Star plans are not in the main computer.
Where are those transmissions you intercepted?
What have you done with those plans?
We intercepted no transmissions.
This is a consular ship. We're on a diplomatic mission.
If this is a consular ship, where is the ambassador?
Commander, tear this ship apart until you've found those plans!
And bring me the passengers! I want them alive!
There's one. Set for stun.
She'll be all right.
Inform Lord Vader we have a prisoner.
Hey. You're not permitted in there. It's restricted.
You'll be deactivated for sure.
Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight glob of grease.
Come out, before somebody sees you.
Secret mission? What plans?
What are you talking about? I'm not getting in there.
I'm going to regret this.
- There goes another one. - Hold your fire. There's no life-forms.
It must have short-circuited.
That's funny. The damage doesn't look as bad from out here.
Are you sure this thing is safe?
Darth Vader. Only you could be so bold.
The Imperial Senate will not sit still for this. When they hear you've attacked a diplomatic--
Don't act so surprised, Your Highness.
You weren't on any mercy mission this time.
Several transmissions were beamed to this ship by rebel spies.
I want to know what happened to the plans they sent you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm a member of the Imperial Senate on a diplomatic mission to Alderaan.
You are part of the Rebel Alliance and a traitor.
Take her away!
Holding her is dangerous.
If word of this gets out, it could generate sympathy for the rebellion in the senate.
I have traced the rebel spies to her.
Now she is my only link to finding their secret base.
She'll die before she'll tell you anything.
Leave that to me.
Send a distress signal, and then inform the senate that all aboard were killed.
Lord Vader, the battle station plans are not aboard this ship...
and no transmissions were made.
An escape pod was jettisoned during the fighting, but no life-forms were aboard.
She must have hidden the plans in the escape pod.
Send a detachment down to retrieve them. See to it personally, Commander.
There'll be no one to stop us this time.